

ROBERT KIRSZ

Frontend Developer Warsaw, Poland

Email: robert.kirsz@gmail.com

Website: robertkirsz.pl

LinkedIn: <u>linkedin.com/in/robertkirsz</u>
GitHub: <u>github.com/robertkirsz</u>

SKILLS

- Working experience in building single page applications (SPA) in React + Redux + React Router using ES6/7 features, bundled together with Webpack
- Personal experience with creating progressive web applications (PWA) in Vue + Vuex + Vue Router
- Writing modular, maintainable CSS with Sass, CSS Modules and/or styled-components
- Creating fully responsive user interfaces
- DOM manipulation with jQuery and native JavaScript
- Knowledge of Bootstrap, Bulma, Skeleton, Material UI for React and Vue and similar frameworks
- Experience with Firebase Authentication, Realtime Database, Storage and Functions APIs
- Expercience in working with REST APIs
- Basics of creating native mobile apps with React Native
- Familiarity with Scrum workflow
- High attention to writing clean, well formatted code with a help from ESLint and Prettier
- Gravitating towards functional and declarative programming
- Knowledge of Git as a version control system
- Ease of use of Adobe Photoshop for converting PSD files to code
- Knowledge of Windows and macOS systems
- Basic knowledge of Grunt and Gulp build systems
- Familiarity with Trello and ScrumDo platforms
- Experience in delivering online demos and product presentations in Polish and English

LANGUAGES

- Native Polish
- Upper intermediate English (B2)

SUMMARY

Frontend developer especially interested in working with UI and UX, creating rich, involving and accessible interfaces for progressive web apps.

Developed fully functional, responsive applications based on business requirements, delivered in HTML, CSS and JavaScript, using mainly React with Redux.

Participated in projects in all stages of the product lifecycle, from design to deployment. Gained experience in creating projects from scratch, as well as working with and maintaining existing codebases.

EXPERIENCE

MobileWeb Pro

Gliwice, Poland (remote worker) - since November 2015

Creating web and native applications in React and React Native - from the ground up, as well as adding new functionalities to the existing ones. Working on projects for international clients from Germany, Belgium, Italy and the United States.

K-EX Sp. z o.o.

Warsaw, Poland - February 2012 - March 2015 (3 years and 2 months)

Coordinated logistics of transport and courier parcels for Polkomtel Sp. z o.o. (Plus mobile network operator)

P.H.U. Aigel-Tools

Warsaw, Poland - March 2011 - January 2012 (10 months)

Created visual identity for the client, created advertising materials (leaflets, catalogues) using Adobe Photoshop and InDesign

Black Tangerine Advertising Agency

Warsaw, Poland - September 2011 - December 2011 (4 months)

Involved in designing advertising materials for clients (Bakoma and DecoMorreno among others), created website for the agency

EDUCATION

Wyższa Szkoła Technologii Informatycznych w Warszawie

(Upper School of Information Technology in Warsaw) 2006 - 2013

Achieved Engineer's Degree in Information Technology Specialization: Computer Graphics and DTP Engineer's Thesis: Creating multimedial web application in HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript

Liceum Ogólnokształcące nr 79 (ZS nr 48) w Warszawie

(79th High School in Warsaw) 2003 - 2006

Class profile: Mathematics and Information Technology